You'll see that this tool looks very, very similar to other chatbots that we had, and this is not a surprise, you know.
All of them look basically the same, so we have an input over here, and here is return perplexity.
So it says, "Ask anything, type, add, sign, for mentions."
And as you see over here, we have modes. So we have the search mode, which generates fast answers to everyday questions.
We also have research mode, so it's about deep research on any topic, and we have labs, which creates projects from scratch, right?
And over here, what do we have? We have dictation mode, we have voice mode, so very similar with what we had with chat GPT, we have an option, an ability to attach files.
We also have the ability to choose a model and set sources for search.
So at first, let's see the most used items of this very AI tool.
So comparison, fact check, and local, sports, and latest news are the ones and are the most common use cases for this AI tool, as you see.
We can also sign in over here, or create an account, to unlock pro search and history, right?
But I don't want to do that for now. We just want to try it, right?